#### Contact

+46720108637 (Mobile) simonnjern@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/simon-jern (LinkedIn)

www.simonjern.com (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Web services REST APIs Material UI

### Languages

English (Full Professional)

Japanese (Limited Working)

Swedish (Native or Bilingual)

# Simon Jern

Software Developer

Malmo, Skåne County, Sweden

## Summary

I am soon completing a Bachelor's degree in System Development at Malmö University, where I am expanding my knowledge and skills in object-oriented systems, full stack web development, and several programming languages such as Java, C#, Kotlin, Python and Javascript. I am looking forward to applying my learning to real-world projects and challenges. Previously, I worked as a Training Manager, where I educated and followed up with new staff and handled various operational and financial tasks.

Having spent several years in Japan, I bring a strong work ethic, adaptability, and effective communication skills to diverse settings. I am fluent in Swedish, English, and Japanese, and have a background in game and interactive media design. My unique blend of experiences enables me to contribute meaningfully to any task I'm presented with.

https://simonjern.com

## Experience

Freelance

Java Programming Instructor September 2021 - Present (2 years 9 months)

I provide tailored Java programming lessons to diverse students, from children to university level. I teach Java concepts, develop curriculums and offer assignment support.

Malmö universitet Course Assistant November 2023 - February 2024 (4 months)

Malmö, Skåne län, Sverige

Assisted the professor in a course about web services. Grading of projects and essays about REST API:s, Web Services and others.

Surf Shack

3 years 6 months

Training Manager

September 2019 - March 2022 (2 years 7 months)

Sweden

As the Training Manager for Surf Shack, my primary responsibility was to educate and follow up with new chefs, service staff, and managers across the entire organization. I also played a key role in franchise development by working on personnel structure, policy creation, and digitization of work processes.

In addition, I was responsible for the most successful unit within the franchise, which entailed handling scheduling, budgeting, HACCP, quality control, ordering, customer support, and much more. At this unit I significantly lowered the waiting time for the customers, raising the overall customer satisfaction.

Restaurant Manager

October 2018 - September 2019 (1 year)

Malmö, Skåne County, Sweden

I was responsible for overseeing daily operations and ensuring the delivery of dining experiences to our guests. My duties included staff management and development, inventory control, financial performance analysis, and maintaining compliance with health and safety regulations. I played a significant role in driving sales growth, customer satisfaction and continuous process improvement.

## Education

Malmö University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science with specialization in Computer Systems Development · (August 2021 - June 2024)

Umeå University

Development of mobile applications · (June 2023 - August 2023)

Nihongo Center

Japanese Studies · (2015 - 2016)

LBS Kreativa Gymnasiet

High School Diploma, Game and Interactive Media Design · (2012 - 2015)